{
    "subject": "Jacques_Feyder",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Carnival_in_Flanders__film_",
    "human_readable": "Jacques Feyder created the film Carnival in Flanders.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.859233558177948,
            "question": "What is the title of the film created by Jacques Feyder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8415821194648743,
            "question": "Who directed the film Carnival in Flanders?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6174581050872803,
            "question": "Where was Carnival in Flanders probably filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5907285809516907,
            "question": "What themes might be explored in Carnival in Flanders?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5725191831588745,
            "question": "What genre is the film Carnival in Flanders likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4967058002948761,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors who appeared in Carnival in Flanders?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4335477650165558,
            "question": "Can you name another film directed by Jacques Feyder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3994288444519043,
            "question": "What time period is the film Carnival in Flanders likely set in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37138044834136963,
            "question": "How is Carnival in Flanders remembered today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3696174621582031,
            "question": "What awards or recognition did Carnival in Flanders receive?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jacques Feyder created the film Carnival in Flanders.",
            "html": "yago_8589_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Carnival in Flanders remembered today?",
            "html": "yago_8589_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What time period is the film Carnival in Flanders likely set in?",
            "html": "yago_8589_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another film directed by Jacques Feyder?",
            "html": "yago_8589_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8589_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8589_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8589_153.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8589_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8589_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8589_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8589_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8589_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8589_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8589_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Jacques Feyder and his creation of the film \"Carnival in Flanders,\" also known as \"La Kermesse h\u00e9ro\u00efque.\" Therefore, the statement that Jacques Feyder created the film Carnival in Flanders is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}